http://www.relpro.com/terms-of-service/

Schedule a Demo
This site uses cookies to provide you with a great user experience. By
visiting RelPro, you accept our
use of cookies.
Terms of Use
Effective Date:
May 17, 2018
Relationship Capital Partners, Inc. (“Relcapp”) & it’s 100%-owned affiliate, RelPro, Inc. (“RelPro”) are dedicated to providing our customers with outstanding customer service and uncompromising privacy protection.  For this reason, we believe you should understand the terms of use that we have adopted to help us provide you with that level of service. Our Terms of Use establish your rights and obligations as a user of our website.
Binding Agreement
PLEASE READ THE FOLLOWING TERMS AND CONDITIONS CAREFULLY.  You are viewing a page of the relcapp.com or the relpro.com web sites belonging to Relationship Capital Partners, Inc. (“Relcapp”) and RelPro, Inc. (“RelPro”), respectively, or a related web site (the “Sites”). These Sites and any of the services provided by Relcapp and RelPro in connection with the Sites (the “Services”) are being provided to you expressly subject to these Terms of Use. Please read these Terms of Use carefully. By accessing this Site you agree to be bound by these Terms of Use. In addition to these Terms of Use you agree to be bound by any other Policies and Terms of Use that may be applicable to other Relcapp or RelPro-owned sites and applications that you may use.
“Services” under these Terms of Use include all of the features and capabilities offered by Relcapp and RelPro, as well as integrations with other software providers. These terms of use will apply to all users accessing any Relcapp or RelPro Site.
General Rules of User Conduct
It is our goal to make the use of our Site and Services a good experience for all of our users, so you agree not to do any of the following:
conduct or promote any illegal activities while using the Site or Services;
post on or through the website, or transmit to any other user or Relcapp / RelPro employee, agent, or representative, any defamatory, inaccurate, abusive, obscene, profane, offensive, sexually oriented, threatening, harassing, racially offensive, or illegal material;
post, distribute or reproduce in any way any copyrighted material, trademarks, or other proprietary information without obtaining the prior written consent of the owner of such proprietary rights;
post, distribute, or reproduce any material that infringes or violates another party’s rights (including, but not limited to, intellectual property rights and rights of privacy and publicity).
attempt to reverse engineer or jeopardize the correct functioning of the Site or Services, or otherwise attempt to derive the source code of the software (including the tools, methods, processes, and infrastructure) that enables or underlies the Site;
attempt to gain access to secured portions of the Site or Services to which you do not possess access rights;
upload or transmit any form of virus, worm, Trojan horse, or other malicious code;
use any automatic or manual process to search or harvest information from the Site or Services, or to interfere in any way with the proper functioning of the Site and Services; or
impersonate another user.
Copyrights/Trademarks/Restrictions on Use
All of the pages and screens on the Site are owned and controlled by Relcapp or RelPro, except as otherwise expressly stated, and are protected by U.S. copyright laws and international treaties. The copyrighted materials on the Site include, but are not limited to, the text, design, software, images, graphics, source code, and the content on the Site. You are authorized to view the information available on the Site for your informational purposes only. You may download copyrighted materials for your personal or internal business purposes only. You acknowledge that you do not acquire any ownership rights by downloading copyrighted material. Except as provided in the User Agreement between Relcapp or RelPro and you, as a registered User, you may not copy, display, distribute, transfer, link to, reproduce, license, frame, alter, create derivative works of or republish all or any portion of the Site for any commercial or public purpose without Relcapp or RelPro’s prior written consent. You may not use, copy, display, distribute, modify or reproduce any of the trademarks found on the Site except as authorized in this paragraph. You may not use any of the Relcapp or RelPro trademarks as a link to the Site except pursuant to a written trademark license agreement.
The Site may contain links to Web sites controlled or offered by third parties (non-affiliates of Relcapp or RelPro). Relcapp and RelPro hereby disclaim liability for any other company’s Web site content, products, privacy policies, or security. In the event you choose to use the services available at a linked site, you agree to read and adhere to the policies and terms of use applicable to that site. In addition, any advice, opinions, or recommendations provided by the linked site providers are those of the providers and not of Relcapp or RelPro. Your participation in any linked site, including payment for and the delivery of goods or services, is based solely on the agreement, if any, between you the linked site provider.
Privacy
Our Privacy Policy explains how we collect, use and disclose information that pertains to your privacy. The Privacy Policy forms part of our agreement with you and is incorporated in this Agreement by reference. For full details, please refer to our Privacy Policy.
Any communications between you and Relcapp or RelPro, such as email or other correspondence, in which you offer suggestions or comments for improving or modifying our Services will be deemed by us to be non-confidential and non-proprietary, and you agree that such information may be used by us without any limitation whatsoever.
For users who are located in the European Union and Switzerland, from May 25th, 2018, all processing of Your personal data by RelPro will be performed in accordance with privacy rights and regulations following the Regulations (EU) 2016/679 of the European Parliament and of the Council of 27 April 2016 on the protection of natural persons with regard to the processing of personal data and on the free movement of such data, known as the General Data Protection Regulation (“GDPR”).
Links to Third Party Sites
Our Site may contain links to third party websites that are not owned, operated, or controlled by Relcapp or RelPro. Therefore, we cannot and do not assume responsibility for the content, privacy policies, or practices of such websites or the companies that own them. Additionally, we cannot and will not censor or edit the content of any third party site. By using the Site or Services you expressly relieve us from any and all liability arising from your use of any third party website.
Third Party Products and Services
Relcapp or RelPro may from time to time promote or offer services and/or products of a third party.  In no event shall Relcapp or RelPro be liable for any incidental, indirect, special, incidental, exemplary, punitive or consequential damages arising out of your purchase, inability to purchase, or use of such third party services or products.
Disclaimer
THE SERVICES ARE OFFERED ON AN “AS IS,” “WHERE IS” AND “WHERE AVAILABLE” BASIS, WITH NO WARRANTY OF ANY KIND-WHETHER EXPRESS, IMPLIED OR STATUTORY-INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, WARRANTIES OF TITLE OR THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY OR FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE. THIS DOES NOT AFFECT THOSE WARRANTIES WHICH INCAPABLE OF EXCLUSION, RESTRICTION OR MODIFICATION UNDER THE LAWS APPLICABLE TO THIS AGREEMENT.
YOU ACKNOWLEDGE THAT NEITHER RELCAPP, RELPRO, THEIR AFFILIATES NOR ANY OF THEIR RESPECTIVE EMPLOYEES, AGENTS, THIRD PARTY CONTENT PROVIDERS OR LICENSORS WARRANT THAT THE SERVICES OR THE SITE WILL BE UNINTERRUPTED OR ERROR FREE; NOR DO THEY MAKE ANY WARRANTY AS TO THE RESULTS THAT MAY BE OBTAINED FROM USE OF THE SERVICES OR THE SITE, OR AS TO THE TIMELINESS, SEQUENCE, ACCURACY, RELIABILITY, COMPLETENESS OR CONTENT OF ANY INFORMATION, SERVICE, OR MERCHANDISE PROVIDED THROUGH THE SERVICES AND THE SITE. RELCAPP AND RELPRO DO NOT ENDORSE PRODUCTS OR SERVICES APPEARING ON LINKED SITES OR PURCHASED VIA LINKED SITES (THIS DOES NOT AFFECT ANY MANUFACTURER’S WARRANTIES THAT THE PROVIDERS OF THE LINKED SITES OTHERWISE OFFER.)
EXCEPT AS SPECIFICALLY PROVIDED IN THIS AGREEMENT OR WHERE THE LAW REQUIRES A DIFFERENT STANDARD, YOU AGREE THAT RELCAPP AND RELPRO ARE NOT RESPONSIBLE FOR ANY LOSS, PROPERTY DAMAGE OR BODILY INJURY, WHETHER CAUSED BY ACCESS TO OR USE OF THE SERVICES OR THE SITE. TO THE MAXIMUM EXTENT PERMISSIBLE UNDER APPLICABLE LAW, RELCAPP AND RELPRO WILL NOT BE RESPONSIBLE TO YOU OR ANY THIRD PARTY CLAIMING THROUGH YOU FOR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, SPECIAL OR CONSEQUENTIAL, ECONOMIC OR OTHER DAMAGES ARISING IN ANY WAY OUT OF THE INSTALLATION OR USE OF THE SERVICES, THE SITE, ANY ON-LINE SERVICES OR INTERNET BROWSER SOFTWARE, INCLUDING LIABILITY ASSOCIATED WITH ANY COMPUTER VIRUSES WHICH MAY INFECT YOUR COMPUTER SYSTEM.
THIS DISCLAIMER OF LIABILITY APPLIES TO ANY DAMAGES OR LOSS, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO THOSE CAUSED BY ANY FAILURE OF PERFORMANCE, ERROR, OMISSION, INTERRUPTION, DELETION, DEFECT, DELAY IN OPERATION OR TRANSMISSION, COMPUTER VIRUS, COMMUNICATION LINE FAILURE, THEFT OR DESTRUCTION OR UNAUTHORIZED ACCESS TO, ALTERATION OF, OR USE OF INFORMATION, WHETHER CAUSED BY SOFTWARE, HARDWARE OR OTHERWISE, AND WHETHER FOR BREACH OF CONTRACT, TORT, STRICT LIABILITY, NEGLIGENCE, OR UNDER ANY OTHER CAUSE OF ACTION.
ANY MATERIAL DOWNLOADED OR OTHERWISE OBTAINED FROM OR THROUGH THE USE OF OUR WEBSITE IS DONE AT YOUR OWN DISCRETION AND RISK. YOU WILL BE SOLELY RESPONSIBLE FOR ANY DAMAGE TO YOUR COMPUTER SYSTEM OR OTHER DEVICE OR FOR LOSS OF DATA THAT RESULTS FROM THE DOWNLOAD OF ANY SUCH MATERIAL. THE WEBSITE MAY CONTAIN BUGS, ERRORS, PROBLEMS OR OTHER LIMITATIONS.
Use by Children under the Age of 13
Relcapp and RelPro are committed to complying fully with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act. Accordingly, if a user of this website is under the age of thirteen, that user is not authorized to provide us with personally identifying information.  Users under the age of thirteen and their parents or guardians are cautioned that the collection of personal information volunteered by unauthorized children online or by e-mail will be treated the same as information voluntarily given by an adult until Relcapp or RelPro becomes aware that the user is under the age of thirteen.  This website is not directed at children under the age of 13. If you are younger than 13, please do not provide any personally identifying information in connection with your use of this website.
Revisions to Terms of Use
Relcapp and RelPro reserve the right to revise these Terms of Use at any time without notice, but the most current version of the Terms of Use will always be available to you by clicking on the link at the bottom of the Site. If you find the Terms of Use unacceptable at any time, you should discontinue your access to the Site and Services. By continuing to access the Site and Services after the date of any change to these Terms of Use, you agree to be bound by the rules contained in the most recent version of this Agreement.
Termination
We may change or discontinue the Site or any of the Services at any time without prior notice. We reserve the right to terminate this Terms of Use at our election and for any reason, without prior notice, and this Agreement will automatically terminate in the event that you violate any of the terms and conditions set forth below. In the event of any termination, you will immediately cease access to the Site and Services.
Indemnification
You agree to defend, indemnify and hold harmless Relcapp and RelPro, their affiliates and their respective directors, officers, employees and agents from and against all claims, losses, damages, costs and expenses, including attorneys’ fees, arising out of your violation of these Terms of Use, Privacy Policy, User Agreement, or misuse of the Service or this Site, including such violation or misuses conducted by your employee or agent, if applicable.
Governing Law
These Terms of Use constitute a contract between you and Relcapp or RelPro governed by the laws of the State of New Jersey.
Relcapp and RelPro’s failure to insist upon or enforce strict performance of any provision of these Terms and Conditions shall not constitute a waiver of the provision. Neither a course of dealing or conduct between you and Relcapp or RelPro nor any trade practices shall be deemed to modify these Terms and Conditions.
Read what our experts are blogging.
see more
posts
